foreign
[Music]
good morning and welcome to opening bell
I'm Stacey Pereira I'm here to take you
through the news and cues that could
impact your trading day well let's get
started then we did see The Benchmark
indices get off to a good start for the
June series on a Friday and it is likely
that that momentum will continue now the
Nifty is closed just shy of that 18 500
Mark and we also saw the sensex so
mounting that 62 500 Peak as for the
bank Nifty that took close about that 44
000 levels
and there could be potential further up
upward movement is what we're looking at
but let's look at the events that
transpired over the weekend where we did
see U.S politicians uh you know reach
that tentative agreement when it comes
to raising the debt ceiling uh that they
have raised it for another two years so
that's going to continue till 2025 and
they've also decided to cut down on
spins now that was The crucial part that
would take uh things forward now the
deal is now ready to move towards the
Congress uh for a vote uh in the days to
come we're going to see how the U.S
treasury really uh you know they could
run out of Cash June 5th was that
deadline uh that they were trying to
meet June 1st but they would have those
extra days but now that they've reached
to this deal it remains to be seen how
the Congress which is really uh divided
you could say to the T will take this
forward however the U.S markets will be
closed today for the Memorial Day
holiday
but back home we do have a couple of big
earnings to be watching out for we have
IRCTC we also have adani ports as well
as adani transmission and cargo
Logistics all of them will be declaring
their Q4 results uh through the day and
if we have to see the trade set up as a
whole well we do have the foreign
institutional investors they have been
the net buyers of equities in the last
three months you could say so and so far
uh for the month of May we've been
seeing around equities have been brought
to the tune of around 37 317 crore just
in May alone and the domestic
institutional investors are no less
they're also throwing their weight
behind Indian markets you could say
continuing to be a net buyers as a whole
but let's get going and discuss some
more strategies and stocks uh that we
are likely to see in Spotlight today
joining me is Prashant sawant of
catalyst wealth Prashant thank you so
much for speaking to us this morning now
given that uh strong momentum that we've
been seeing and you know that break that
we've been seeing in the last it is a
consolidation one would say as a whole
for the indices is it likely to be
marching towards that 18 700 18 800
levels in the coming days where do you
see the support and resistance
uh Stacy good morning and good morning
to all the viewers I think it has been a
fantastic rally after some consolidation
towards the Karnataka elections the way
we took off from Friday has been very
strong and if you look at Nifty now to
share the major levels if you look at
the June Futures we closed at somewhere
around 80 000 575. I think uh looking at
the Gap up we might be touching
somewhere around
18710 so on the upside I think 18 800 to
840 happens to be a big resistance now
one word of caution here what happens is
we emotionally try to hold for 19 000
which is just hundred points away once
we reach 18 850. so the logical step
would be to trade closely and if there
is a reversal of profits and wait for
some time at the same time looking at
the strength in the indices and
especially Bank Nifty I would definitely
say that it's a good time to look at
opportunities in individual sectors and
individual stocks so some of the sectors
like Auto they have been doing
phenomenally well as well as Banks so
PSU banking may do really well so you
can keep an eye here I think overall the
wheel the one interesting and most
important stock which needs to be on
your radar is reliance because I think
there definitely has to be a catch-up
rally with Nifty also trying to Shire
near the all-time high so for that
Reliance will be a major contributor and
I think the HDFC twins as well so an
interesting week ahead personal that
Prashant will get to each stock specific
and you know strategies that one should
be looking at but let's look at the bank
Nifty you spoke about it we're seeing a
support levels at uh forty three
thousand seven hundred so we did see it
cross that 44 uh thousand Peak as well
so are not potential uptrend but what
could be the factors that could play
spoils 45 to be the devil's advocate
here uh we have the upcoming June fed uh
meet as well could that really change
the way things are moving for the
banking sector back home as also the
bank Nifty as an index
so I think the very simple logic one
needs to follow now is if Bank Nifty
closes today about the all-time high so
say in future if we close somewhere
around 44 44 500. the very basic logic
one needs to follow is keep your stop
loss which would now we are trading stop
loss slightly below 44 000 so say 43 950
980 Zone and hold so as long as you are
not risking anything you are holding
your position and just thrilling if this
is a reversal you will book out so
before and uh one thing which I always
religiously follow is if there is any
planned event in the market it's always
advisable to book your profit once come
out of the market and re-enter after the
event overall I think most of the
investors and the Traders those who are
holding on to their long position would
be decent profits so always okay
we have the market open and light was
suggesting it is opening in the green
going up there to that
18608 that's the opening Point uh up
almost half a percentage more than half
one sixth four percent you could say but
definitely a good start to the week of
course and that's what we were expecting
and quite a few uh Global cues to be
taking uh that forward we saw from the
U.S what came off that deal that was
something that the markets were
anticipating and it could take things in
either way even the sensex there at that
62 978 so that's almost uh 0.78 percent
higher the mid cap broader indices also
mirroring what the benchmarks have done
there that two up half a percentage
point you can see the mid cap they're
half a percentage point and the Nifty
also moving upwards you could say so new
levels being breached you could say that
we were at a five month high or you
could say 2023 highs so looking at that
moving upwards look at the Blue Chip
stocks those two are looking uh you know
clearly in the green Reliance that was
one stock that you said to watch out for
and uh viewers can see that too in the
green m m if you look at Auto stocks
that too up there by three percent so
that is one stock that had come under
pressure after its earnings but now uh
in the green Infosys for that matter
here again among the it packed but that
one also in the green HDFC Bank doing
well now we do have to look at the
banking back because we we are getting a
lot of news from that whole thing there
is a news buzzing around ICICI Bank so
um that one buying up stake in uh ICICI
Lombard which is its subsidiary so that
is something that we're going to be
looking at for that counter there on
your screens also uh taking much higher
both of them for that matter I see I say
Lombard as well as uh I see I say a bank
but let's look at sectoral indices and
how they are performing uh well we can
see uh the bank Nifty of course in that
uptrend let's look at the auto pack the
Nifty Auto that too in the green we did
see m m one of the stocks doing pretty
well how about metals that is a counter
that needs to be watched out for so we
are going to have to see how that one
really takes it on that is something
we're going to be looking out for how
about the fmcg pack that is also
something that we need to be looking out
for now let's look at the gainers for uh
today as trade starts this week the
Nifty gainers what do we have there we
have adani Enterprise that one's again
ticking upwards in forces of any ports
we are going to see them declared their
Q4 results so adani ports is something
that we will be on a radar adani
transmission too is something that is uh
some a company that is going to be
looking at its Q4 results how about
losers let's look at the counter for
losers we are seeing ongc Sun Pharma as
well as divi's lab now we are going to
get into the specifics of why these
counters are low omgc reported that
one-time loss of almost 9 thousand
crores and that is perhaps what is
taking it lower power grid cipla Pharma
pack as a whole is seeing a lot of
consolidation one would say a lot of
counters there that are on the radar so
let me go back uh to Prashant now and
get his views on how he is looking at
this he did give us the technical
viewers to what uh levels we are
supposed to be looking at but uh
Prashant how are you looking at this
Monday morning opening cues like you
were pointing out all those blue chips
really uh in the green again but what
should our viewers really be looking at
what should Traders be looking at for
what factors
uh Stacy I think a couple of stocks
which have been on my radar are one is
astral I think it's a good positional
buy from here for targets around 18 40
1860 and one can maintain a stop loss at
1735 along with that I see good strength
in mid cap Nifty So birla Soft which is
terminal the code is B soft you can look
at the stop loss around 328 inch pause
and it may go up to 355 360. so I think
a couple of stocks look good metals are
picking up but I would say wait for the
day let them go sustain tomorrow you can
start looking at Metals as well for now
I think astral and Villas would be my
two pitch
right so those are the picks coming uh
from Prashant but let's take a look at
some of the stocks like we were
discussing now I told you there's a lot
happening in that banking space and we
have ICICI Bank which is among which
today the board has gone ahead and
approved increasing the stake in ICICI
Lombard by about four percent now this
has happened over multiple tranches
remember ICICI Bank holds about 48.2
percent in ICICI Lombard this is as of
31st March and with this stake hi guys
will become a subsidiary of the bank
this will of course be subject to those
necessary approvals now another stock
that we're talking about the farmer pack
like I was saying is Lupine now that is
the stock that one should be watching
out for among the farmer ones that's
because it's Canadian subsidiary that is
uh has received the approval from Health
Canada and this is to Market a generic
version of this Spiriva drug in Canada
now the drug is used for patients with
the chronic obstructive pulmonary
diseases and this includes a chronic
bronchitis as well as M cephism now
speaking of uh more in that Pharma story
well we do have Sun Pharma
and that counter definitely there in the
red as you can see and this is because
they have gone ahead and said that they
would like they've issued a letter to
the board of tarot Pharmaceuticals which
is that Israeli company with the
proposal of a non-binding indication of
interest to acquire the remaining shares
in Tarot through a reverse triangular
merge and out to this transaction they
will it will take place in a cash
transaction at a price of 38 dollars per
share which if I have to say is a
premium of about a 31 of taro's closing
price as of May 25th now the following
the completion of this proposal uh the
facade farmer will become a hundred
percent stake they will hold 100 stake
in Tarot and moving on then that stock
that I was talking about uh which is
down and about is again on GC among the
top losers today and that is because the
state-owned oil and gas exploration
company has posted a standalone loss of
about
247.7 crore in quarter four this is
being dented by the huge one-time loss
that they've taken of 9
305 crore now the weak Top Line as well
as that lower than expected operating
performance is what has also impacted
the bottom line whereas you get the
Standalone revenue from operations for
the fourth quarter that has come in at
36 293 crore this too has fallen by
about 5.9 percent compared to a year ago
so you can see that counter still taking
on the chin down about five percent in
trade today and it's gonna get a
dropping a further you could say but all
of this not only are going too well for
the stock I perhaps will go back uh to
Prashant and ask him he did give us his
picks but let's uh look at some more
technicals now Prashant did give us your
two stop picks but if you look at these
counters what should our viewers be
looking out for we did pick out these
stocks because they are in news and
buzzing but how would you look at you
know what would be your picks among uh
the broader these Blue Chip stocks if I
have to ask
so uh I think Stacy if we talk about
ondc definitely there is a natural
reaction to the results and I think it
has come to decent levels if you see
currently it's putting around 158 in
sport and uh any any level between 150
by 160 would be a good buy your stock
loss has to be 150 on closing basis and
I think if it picks up from here you can
go to the previous High somewhere around
170. so definitely a good level to add
well so on GC will be a counter that
we'll be looking out for there are quite
a few others like I mentioned uh
earnings that are going to be in Focus
IRCTC for that matters something that
we're going to be looking out for that
counter if you have to look at uh you
know over a three year period has
definitely given some really good
returns but has succumbed to recent
pressures at least if you have to look
at that counter in the last five days
and not looking to promising but
definitely has uh and a reason to be
going forward with the whole uh you know
summer vacation season so a lot to be
looking out for adani ports as well as
Transmissions both of those counters
will definitely also be in Focus let's
look at another PSU stock that is in
Focus that is of a bhel now bhel's uh Q4
profits those are the ones that tanked
about 33 on a year on year basis coming
in at uh 611 crores this on the back of
a week operating numbers we also saw a
tepid 2 Top Line growth in fact revenues
just at about two percent at eight
thousand two hundred and twenty seven
crores so that is something that we're
going to be looking out for when it
comes to these stocks and the rest of
the day but those opening cues there for
you the Nifty uh comfortably there in
the green even the sensex to treading
higher you could save from those levels
Nifty right now at 18
617 the sensex at 62
943 definitely could even surpass and
get to that 63
000 levels Bank Nifty two at a
comfortably above uh forty four thousand
one could say mid cap small cap both
those broader indices also rarely uh you
know ticking higher so good start one
could say for the week we have a couple
of macro data points that are going to
be very crucial through this week uh
well you do have the the auto sales data
that will be coming up by the end of the
month that's when we normally see that
we also have the FED meeting when you
come to the international front the June
fair meeting is going to be crucial but
we also have the GDP numbers now our q1
GDP numbers is something that is going
to be on everyone's mind at least the
economist so that is something that we
are going to be keeping you in a track
with well that's all we have on this
edition of opening bell but more news
and updates will continue right here
keep watching money control as well as
us on the money control app thanks for
everyone for tuning in
[Music]
oh
foreign